// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Why is listening such an important ability to have?",
    answer: "To avoid miscommunications",
    options: [
      "To avoid miscommunications",
      "To listen to our favorite music",
      "To become a better speaker",
      "To become more interested in a topic"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the reason on why we listen?",
    answer: "To learn new information",
    options: [
      "To entertain ourselves",
      "To become a better speaker",
      "To learn new information",
      "To remember what we learned before"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What type of textual aid is in the form of rows and columns?",
    answer: "Table",
    options: [
      "Table",
      "Graph",
      "Title",
      "Structure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is not part of the setting of the story?",
    answer: "Conflict",
    options: [
      "The place",
      "Conflict",
      "The time",
      "The weather"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is chronological order?",
    answer: "The sequence of the story starting from beginning to end",
    options: [
      "Hint of the future hidden in the beginning of the story",
      "The highest point of the story",
      "The lowest point of the story",
      "The sequence of the story starting from beginning to end"
    ]
  },
     {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What is the dispute between opposing forces?",
     answer: "Conflict",
     options: [
       "War",
       "Destruction",
       "Conflict",
       "Climax"
     ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the highest point of the story?",
    answer: "Climax",
    options: [
      "Conflict",
      "Foreshadowing",
      "Ending",
      "Climax"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is foreshadowing?",
    answer: "Hint of the future hidden in the beginning of the story",
    options: [
      "The conclusion of the story",
      "Hint of the future hidden in the beginning of the story",
      "A scary story",
      "A summary of what happened in the past"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the tool that can help readers understand the meaning of the text?",
    answer: "Textual Aids",
    options: [
      "Textual Aids",
      "Google translate",
      "Encyclopedia",
      "ChatGPT"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What type of graphic organizer depicts the process of a certain topic or idea?",
    answer: "Flow chart",
    options: [
      "Fishbone diagram",
      "Concept Map",
      "Venn diagram",
      "Flow chart"
    ]
  },
];